vodafone.com.gh 2018-06-15

# Privacy Statement

Vodafone Ghana takes the privacy of its customers seriously. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy whilst providing a personalized and valuable service

**Overview**

This Privacy Statement explains the data processing practices of Vodafone Ghana.If you have any requests concerning your Personal Information or any questions about these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at _._ We encourage you to periodically review this Statement as Vodafone reserves the right to alter or change the terms and information set out in this Statement at any time at its sole discretion.

In the event that you provide us with Personal Information for the purposes of registration or any of our Services, your privacy rights will be protected according to our stated general and privacy policies, which will be posted and available for your review at the time of purchase. Kindly note that your Personal Information shall also represent/mean your personal data (any information relating to you directly or indirectly as an identifiable natural person)

**Information Collected**

Personal information is regularly collected by Vodafone Ghana. We collect personally identifiable information about you (your "Data") through:

_The use of inquiry and registration forms._

_The use of or registration for our products or services_

_The provision of your details to us either online or offline_

Other elements of your Data that we collect may include:

_Name_

_Company name_

_Home, shipping and billing addresses, phone and fax number_

_Mobile telephone number_

_E-mail address_

_IP address and browser information_

_Market research data such as customer usage patterns_

_Use and Disclosure of Personal Information_

**We use your Data for purposes, which may include but are not limited to the following:**

_Providing our customers with a personalized service._

_Processing orders, registrations and inquiries._

_Conducting market research surveys._

_Running competitions._

_Measuring interest in and improving our website, products, and services._

_Providing you with information about products and services we offer._

We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except;

1.      To the extent necessary to complete that order or to provide services where the outside party is acting on our behalf and has no independent right to use the information we provide (e.g., third-party shipping);

2.      To improve service provision, develop new products and enhance our value proposition; or

3.      To successors in title to our business; or 

4.       In accordance with legal and regulatory requirements; or 

5.      As necessary, at Vodafone Ghana’ssole discretion, to protect the perceived rights, safety and property of Vodafone Ghana, users of our websites, and the public.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when Personal Information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

**Security Policy**

Vodafone Ghana has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ Data is protected against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, cyber-crime and accidental loss. Although we make reasonable efforts as a service provider to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. Vodafone shall take reasonable and appropriate technical and organizational measures against the unauthorized or unlawful deliberate interference to Customers’ personal data, however, there is still some risk that criminals could find a way to thwart our security systems.

**Transfer of Data**

The Internet is a global environment. Using the Internet to collect and process Personal Data necessarily involves the transmission of Data on an international basis. When we collect Personal Information from you on our website, we comply with both local and international data protection laws and safeguards. 

**Your privacy rights**

You can write to us at any time to get a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Please complete an application form available either by walking into any of our retail shops or [](https://images//documents/CDR%20REQUEST%20FORM.docx)[ Here](https://documents/CDRREQUESTFORM.docx)

Send the completed form to at no charge. Allow Vodafone seven (7) working days to provide you with the requested information. 

If you wish to change or correct your information or lodge a complaint, please contact our customer care service team through our Contact Us page on our website. 

You may reach out to the Data Protection Commission at [https://www.dataprotection.org.gh/](https://vfghrassolution.vodafone.com.gh/,DanaInfo=www.dataprotection.org.gh,SSL+)  if you feel your privacy rights have been violated. 

**Changes to this Policy**

This Statement takes effect from 1 July 2018. From time to time we may make changes to this Privacy Statement to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes in legislation, regulation, best practice or website enhancements. We will notify you about material changes to this Statement by placing a prominent notice on our website.
